<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AnimeList</string>
    <string name="pokemon_description">The Pokemon series is a long-running and iconic franchise that has captured the hearts of audiences worldwide. It follows the adventures of Ash Ketchum and his loyal Pikachu as they journey through various regions, capturing new Pokemon and competing in battles. The series embodies the spirit of exploration and friendship, emphasizing the importance of teamwork, determination, and the pursuit of one\'s dreams. Ash\'s growth from an inexperienced trainer to a seasoned Pokemon Master is a central theme, and the show introduces a wide array of Pokemon species, each with unique characteristics and abilities. Beyond the exciting battles, the series imparts valuable life lessons, making it not only entertaining but also educational for younger viewers.\n</string>
    <string name="doraemon_description">Doraemon is a heartwarming and enduring series that follows the life of Nobita Nobi, a young boy who faces the challenges of daily life with the help of a robotic cat from the future named Doraemon. Doraemon possesses a vast array of futuristic gadgets that he uses to assist Nobita in navigating the ups and downs of childhood. The series combines humor, imagination, and a touch of sci-fi to create a delightful and educational experience. Through Nobita\'s adventures and misadventures, viewers learn important life lessons and values, such as the significance of hard work, kindness, and the value of friendship. Doraemon\'s ability to make the impossible possible is not only a source of laughter but also a reminder that with creativity and determination, any obstacle can be overcome.\n</string>
    <string name="digimon_description">Digimon Adventures is an exciting and enduring franchise that invites viewers to enter the digital world alongside a group of courageous kids. In this world, they form profound connections with digital creatures known as Digimon. These digital partners not only assist in their survival but also enable them to confront and overcome various threats. Each season introduces a fresh cast of characters and a unique storyline, emphasizing the values of teamwork, bravery, and the enduring power of friendship. The show beautifully combines action, adventure, and heartfelt moments, making it a beloved choice for children and pre-teens. The concept of Digivolution, where Digimon can evolve into more powerful forms, adds an extra layer of excitement and strategy to the series. As the children and their Digimon grow, they face increasingly challenging adversaries, and viewers witness their personal growth and maturation. Digimon Adventures serves as a reminder that true strength comes not only from power but also from the bonds we share with others.</string>
    <string name="beyblade_description">The Beyblade series is an adrenaline-pumping anime centered around spinning top battles. Young Bladers engage in intense tournaments, showcasing their spinning top (Beyblade) skills and strategies. As they compete for supremacy, the series emphasizes the importance of sportsmanship, fair play, and the spirit of healthy competition. Each season introduces new characters, Beyblade types, and exciting battles. Beyblade encourages viewers to pursue their passions, hone their skills, and demonstrate perseverance in the face of challenging opponents.</string>
    <string name="yokai_watch_description">Yo-Kai Watch is a whimsical and imaginative series that introduces viewers to a world filled with Yo-Kai, mischievous supernatural creatures. Nate, the young protagonist, possesses a special Yo-Kai Watch that allows him to see, befriend, and interact with these Yo-Kai. The series takes a lighthearted approach as Nate helps the Yo-Kai with their problems and resolves various comedic and sometimes heartwarming situations. Through these adventures, the show offers valuable lessons about empathy, understanding, and the importance of helping others. Yo-Kai Watch captures the essence of childhood curiosity and the idea that even the most unusual and quirky beings have their own stories to tell.</string>
    <string name="naruto_description">Naruto is an epic journey of self-discovery and perseverance. The series follows Naruto Uzumaki, a spirited ninja-in-training with dreams of becoming the Hokage, the leader of his village. Throughout his adventures, Naruto forms unbreakable bonds with his friends and mentors, all while facing formidable enemies. The show beautifully illustrates themes of friendship, resilience, and the indomitable human spirit, as Naruto overcomes obstacles and strives to protect his loved ones.</string>
    <string name="one_piece_description">One Piece is a grand adventure set in a world of pirates. It follows Monkey D. Luffy and his crew, the Straw Hat Pirates, as they search for the legendary treasure known as the One Piece. The series is renowned for its vast world-building, intricate characters, and epic battles. Beyond the high-seas action, it delves into themes of freedom, camaraderie, and the pursuit of one\'s dreams, making it a beloved series for fans of all ages.\n</string>
    <string name="bleach_description">Bleach is a captivating supernatural series that centers on Ichigo Kurosaki, a young man who acquires the powers of a Soul Reaper. He becomes responsible for defending the living world from malevolent spirits and Hollows. The series combines thrilling battles with intricate character development and moral dilemmas. Ichigo\'s journey explores themes of duty, sacrifice, and the consequences of wielding great power.\n</string>
    <string name="dragon_ball_description">Dragon Ball is an iconic and action-packed franchise that chronicles the adventures of Goku, a martial artist with an unwavering pursuit of becoming the world\'s greatest fighter. The series features high-octane battles, formidable foes, and a quest for Dragon Balls to make wishes. While filled with action, Dragon Ball also explores themes of personal growth, determination, and the enduring spirit of heroism.\n\n</string>
    <string name="hunter_x_hunter_description">Hunter x Hunter is a captivating and versatile series that follows Gon Freecss, a young boy on a quest to become a Hunter and find his missing father. As he navigates the challenges of the Hunter Exam and encounters diverse characters, the series explores themes of exploration, friendship, and self-discovery. The show expertly combines adventure with thought-provoking storytelling and is known for its engaging characters and intricate world-building.\n</string>
    <string name="fruits_basket_description">Fruits Basket is a heartwarming and emotionally resonant series that revolves around Tohru Honda, a kind-hearted girl who stumbles upon a unique family secret. She discovers that the members of the Sohma family are cursed to transform into animals from the Chinese zodiac when hugged by the opposite sex. The series delves into themes of acceptance, healing, and the power of friendship and love. It weaves a tale of personal growth, compassion, and the transformative influence of genuine connections.\n</string>
    <string name="sailor_moon_description">Sailor Moon, also known as Usagi Tsukino, is a legendary magical girl who transforms into Sailor Moon to protect the world from dark forces and evil villains. Alongside her Sailor Senshi friends, she battles for justice and love. The series combines magical girl elements with themes of empowerment and teamwork. Sailor Moon has left an indelible mark on the magical girl genre and is celebrated for its strong, diverse cast of heroines and the messages of love, courage, and female friendship it conveys.\n\n</string>
    <string name="violet_evergarden_description">Violet Evergarden is a beautifully animated and emotionally resonant series that tells the story of Violet, a former soldier who becomes an Auto Memory Doll. Her role is to write heartfelt letters on behalf of clients who struggle to express their emotions. The anime explores themes of empathy, self-discovery, and the power of words. Violet\'s journey is a poignant exploration of the human capacity for healing and connecting with others through the written word.\n</string>
    <string name="banana_fish_description">Banana Fish is a gripping crime drama that revolves around Ash Lynx, a young gang leader, and Eiji Okumura, a Japanese photographer. Together, they unravel the mystery of \"Banana Fish,\" a dangerous and enigmatic drug. The series delves into themes of love, friendship, and the impact of a dark past. With a gritty and intense narrative, Banana Fish is a striking exploration of trauma and the lengths one will go to protect those they care about.\n</string>
    <string name="kaichou_wa_maid_sama_description">Kaichou wa Maid-sama! is a delightful romantic comedy that centers around Misaki Ayuzawa, the strong-willed and independent student council president. To support her family, she secretly works at a maid cafe, which leads to amusing encounters with a male student, Usui Takumi. The series combines humor with themes of personal growth and romance. It explores the idea that individuals can be multifaceted, and strength can be found in embracing one\'s true self.\n</string>
    <string name="berserk_description">Berserk is a dark and mature series that tells the tragic tale of Guts, a lone warrior seeking revenge against his former friend and nemesis, Griffith. The series explores themes of ambition, fate, and the brutal realities of a medieval-inspired world. It\'s renowned for its complex characters and the exploration of the human condition.\n</string>
    <string name="vagabond_description">Vagabond is a historical and character-driven series based on the life of the legendary samurai, Miyamoto Musashi. While it has no anime adaptation, the manga is celebrated for its intricate storytelling, philosophical depth, and the pursuit of enlightenment through the way of the sword. It\'s a deeply philosophical exploration of the human journey.\n</string>
    <string name="vinland_saga_description">Vinland Saga is a historical epic set during the Viking Age. It follows Thorfinn, a young warrior seeking revenge on the man who killed his father. The series explores themes of war, honor, and the pursuit of a peaceful land, Vinland. It offers a gritty and immersive look into history and the personal struggles of its characters.\n</string>
    <string name="monster_description">Monster is a psychological thriller that follows Dr. Kenzo Tenma, a brilliant neurosurgeon. He becomes entangled in a web of conspiracy and murder when he saves the life of a young boy, Johan Liebert, who grows up to become a ruthless serial killer. The series explores moral dilemmas, choices, and the consequences of one\'s actions. It\'s a masterful exploration of human darkness and the choices we make in the face of evil.\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="kaguya_sama_description">Kaguya-sama: Love is War – Ultra Romantic is a delightful romantic comedy that continues the hilarious and strategic battles of Kaguya Shinomiya and Miyuki Shirogane, the high-achieving student council members. They engage in a battle of wits to make the other confess their love first. The series combines humor with themes of love, friendship, and teenage romance. It cleverly portrays the absurdity and complexity of young love, emphasizing that even in the midst of comedic scheming, genuine emotions and affection can emerge.\n</string>
    <string name="rakugo_shinju_description">Descending Stories: Showa Genroku Rakugo Shinju is a poignant and character-driven series that delves into the traditional art of rakugo storytelling. It follows the lives of rakugo performers, their struggles, and the legacy they leave behind. The series explores themes of artistry, tradition, and personal relationships. Rakugo is a traditional form of Japanese storytelling, and the anime offers a unique glimpse into this art form while delving into the personal and professional challenges faced by the performers.\n</string>
    <string name="usagi_drop_description">Usagi Drop is a heartwarming and slice-of-life series that focuses on Daikichi Kawachi, a single man who takes in Rin, a young girl abandoned by her family. The series beautifully portrays the journey of parenthood and the bond that forms between Daikichi and Rin. It explores themes of family, responsibility, and the love that can develop in unconventional circumstances.\n</string>
    <string name="princess_jellyfish_description">Princess Jellyfish is a charming and quirky series that centers around a group of socially awkward women living in an apartment complex. Their lives take a whimsical turn when they befriend Tsukimi Kurashita, who dreams of becoming an illustrator. The series explores themes of friendship, self-acceptance, and pursuing one\'s passions. It celebrates the unique qualities of its characters and the idea that individuals can find acceptance and belonging through shared interests and supportive communities</string>
    <string name="chihayafuru_description">The Chihayafuru series is a sports anime that focuses on the Japanese card game karuta. It follows Chihaya Ayase and her friends as they pursue their passion for karuta and compete in tournaments. The series highlights themes of dedication, competition, and the love of a traditional Japanese sport. Chihayafuru beautifully showcases the art and strategy of karuta while portraying the friendships and rivalries that emerge within the karuta community.\n</string>
    <string name="kids_on_the_slope_description">Kids on the Slope is a coming-of-age series set in the 1960s that centers around Kaoru Nishimi, a high school student, and Sentaro Kawabuchi, a talented jazz drummer. Their shared love for music leads to deep friendships and personal growth. The series explores themes of music, friendship, and the challenges of youth. It combines a passion for jazz music with the trials and tribulations of adolescence, portraying the transformative power of artistic expression and human connection.</string>

    <string name="seasons">seasons: %d</string>
    <string name="episodes">episodes: %d</string>

</resources>